Guide to the Ruby Loper slide collection, 1950-1960.
Loper, Ruby slide collection, 1950-1960.
- Series VI. House Planning, Insulation, Heating and Kitchens
  - Glass slides pertaining to house planning, insulation, heating, and kitchens (Box 4 and 5)